guildmortgage.com 2014-06-11

# F A C T S WHAT DOES GUILD MORTGAGE COMPANY DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

                                                                                                                            Rev. 1/2014
                      WHAT DOES GUILD MORTGAGE COMPANY DO
      FACTS
                      WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
   Why?               Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the
                      right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and
                      protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
   What?              The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.
                      This information can include:
                            Social Security number and income
                            account balances and payment history
                            credit history and credit scores
                      When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
   How?               All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In
                      the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information;
                      the reasons Guild Mortgage Company chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                     Does Guild Mortgage        Can you limit this
                Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                                       Company share?                sharing?
   For our everyday business purposes—
   such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to                   Yes                      No
   court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
   For our marketing purposes—
                                                                                                Yes                      No
   to offer our products and services to you
   For joint marketing with other financial companies                                           Yes                      No
   For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                                Yes                      No
   information about your transactions and experiences
   For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                                No                 We don’t share
   information about your creditworthiness
   For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                           Yes                      Yes
                                  Call (800) 365-4441 – our menu will prompt you through your choice(s)
                                  Mail the form below
                              Please note:
   To limit our
   sharing                    If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent
                              this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                              described in this notice.
                              However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
   Questions?               Call (800) 365-4441 or go to www.guildmortgage.com
----------------------------------------------------------------
   Mail-in Form
   Mark any/all you want to limit:
    Do not share information about my creditworthiness with your affiliates for their everyday business purposes.
    Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me.
    Do not share my personal information with nonaffiliates to market their products and services to me.
   Name                                                                                          Mail to:
   Address                                                                                       Guild Mortgage Company
                                                                                                 Attn: Privacy Opt Out
   City, State, Zip                                                                              PO Box 85304
   Loan #                                                                                        San Diego, CA 92186
GMC 884

Page 2
   Who we are
   Who is providing this notice?                     Guild Mortgage Company
   What we do
   How does Guild Mortgage Company protect           To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use,
   my personal information?                          we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures
                                                     include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
   How does Guild Mortgage Company collect           We collect your personal information, for example, when you
   my personal information?                            apply for a loan or provide account information
                                                       give us your income information or give us your contact information
                                                       provide employment information
                                                     We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                                     bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
   Why can’t I limit all sharing?                    Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                       sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about
                                                           your creditworthiness
                                                       affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                       sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                     State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                     limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
   Definitions
   Affiliates                                        Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                     financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                     Our affiliates include financial companies, such as:
                                                          Guild Financial Express
                                                      And nonfinancial companies, such as:
                                                       Guild Administration Corporation
                                                       Mission Village Insurance
   Nonaffiliates                                     Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                     financial and nonfinancial companies. Nonaffiliated companies we share
                                                     with include:
                                                          Banking and financial institutions, mortgage service providers,
                                                           insurance companies, mortgage companies and direct marketing
                                                           companies
   Joint Marketing                                   A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                                     together market financial products or services to you. Our joint marketing
                                                     partners include:
                                                          Banking institutions
   Other important information
   California Residents – In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with
   companies outside of our corporate family, except as permitted by law, including, for example, with your consent or to
   service your account. We will limit sharing among our companies to the extent required by California law.
   We collect and store only information you provide us that we believe is necessary or appropriate to offer or provide you our
   services and products. We do not collect personal information about your online activities over time and across third party
GMC 884

Page 3
   websites and online services when you use our website, except to the extent that we believe collecting the information
   concerning your visit to the Guild Mortgage Company website is necessary or appropriate to offer or provide you Guild’s
   services and products. We do not track your online activity beyond your activity on the Guild Mortgage Company website.
   Because we do not send your searches to other websites, we effectively honor "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that
   provide you and other consumers with choice regarding the collection of your personal information, by limiting our
   information collection and storage as described above and in our Privacy Notice.
   Nevada Residents - Nevada Statute Section 228.600(3) allows marketing calls to our existing customers listed on the
   National Do Not Call Registry. If you prefer not to receive marketing calls from us, you may be placed on our Internal Do
   Not Call list by following the instructions in the "Your Choices" section 5 above or writing to Guild Mortgage Company,
   Attn: Privacy Opt Out, PO Box 85304, San Diego, CA 92186
   You may also contact the Nevada Attorney General's office:
   Bureau of Consumer Protection Office of the Nevada Attorney General
   555 E. Washington Street, Suite 3900
   Las Vegas, NV 89101
   Phone: (702) 486-3132
   Email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us
GMC 884
